well the RDI has proposed a cap on
tenure of MDS cosos and holdtime
directors for insurance firms so this is
a proposal in draft stage and it is in
line with the RBI rules so the draft
states that almost 70 years would be the
retirement age limit and the tenure uh
will be kept at almost 15 years at one
stretch after the three-year cooling
period the key manager persons can
rejoin their positions now these key
managerial positions if they are a
promoter or holding a 5% stake in the
insurance company they cannot hold the
post going Beyond 12 years however some
extensions can definitely be there as
IID has stated now you see the current
picture we see over here sdfc life
insurance is mdco Viba padalkar is
having an existing tenure of almost 3
years and she's aged at almost 53 even
if you get IC proves NS Canan his
existing tenure last at almost five
years and he's average ages coming up to
almost 50s same thing goes for SBI lives
Mahesh Kumar Sharma however IC Lombards
bav Das Gupta is already having a
13-year existing tenure so that would be
in focus and however star health
insurance uh chairman and mdco W Swami
jaganathan he'll be in focus of course
the company because he has already
completed the 15 years existing tenure
and his age is above the 70 limit at 77
baj islandes tapan single also has
almost 10 years as an existing tenure
and if you just see the whole time
director's picture over here only HDFC
life via pad's numbers we can see almost
9 years she's having that existing
tenure as well but how the age is on her
side at 53